

# **Contact:**

Mobile: +38978452658

Email: apostolovskisimon@gmail.com

## LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/simonapostolovski/

#### GitLab:

https://gitlab.com/apostolovskisimon

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/apostolovskisimon

# **Portfolio**

## https://apostolovskisimon.github.io/

## **Brainster Space**

Project about Brainster's offices, events and courses. Created with CSS, JavaScript and jQuery.

- https://simon-apostolovski-project02.netlify.app/

#### **Case Studies X**

Project about courses and their details. Created with ReactJS and CSS

- https://simon-apostolovski-project03.netlify.app/

## **Periodic System**

A periodic system with details and Macedonian + English support. Created with ReactJS and CSS

- https://simon-apostolovski-project04.netlify.app/

#### **Brainster Marketing Map**

A hackathon project that will connect marketing agencies and marketers. Created with ReactJS and CSS - <a href="https://brainster-fe-hackathon1.netlify.app/">https://brainster-fe-hackathon1.netlify.app/</a>

## **Personal MERN Stack Project**

https://simon-apostolovski-mern-personal.netlify.app/

# Simon Apostolovski

Junior Front End Developer and a Bachelor in E-Business.

I am highly motivated, willing and able to learn new things, but also improve on what I already know and always staying optimistic.

Also, a competent and communicative team player, focused on using my creativity and skills on getting the job done alongside my teammates with correct time management and flexibility.

I focus on ReactJS paired up with SASS or Styled Components that I write on my own as I prefer it, however I'm experienced and can work with the Bootstrap library if needed or learn more about other libraries. I always try to implement something new and find different solutions to the same problems.

# **Work Experience**

#### Intern

NLB AD Skopje | 07/2019 - 10/2019

- Data Processing, Communication with clients, Team Working

#### Intern

NLB AD Skopje | 06/2018 - 07/2018

#### Intern

NLB AD Skopje | 06/2017 - 07/2017

# **Education**

## Brainster (10/2019 - 10/2020)

Front End Academy

### Study program:

HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, React JS. Product management with Agile and Scrum.

# Ss Cyril and Methodius University - Faculty of Economics (09/2016 - 10/2020)

**Bachelor in E-Business** 

#### Study program:

Internet Marketing, Customer Relationship Management, Business Management, Information Technology.

# Skills

- JavaScript
- ReactIS
- CSS3
- SASS
- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- AJAX

# Characteristics

- Team Worker
- Loyal
- Quick Learner
- Responsible
- Positive Attitude
- Creative
- Communicative

# Languages Spoken

#### Macedonian

- Native

## **English**

- Bilingual